NAACP Legal Defense and Educational Fund
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Subject File, 1929-1968 (Box 38-175)
  - Labor
    - Unions
      - Tampa, Fla., investigation See also Container 98, American Federation of Labor investigation
        - Correspondence
          - Special, 1938-1940 (Box 111)
        - Legislation, 1936-1938
        - Press clippings and releases, 1939-1940
    - Yellow Cab Co., 1952-1953
  - Lane Bryant Annual Awards, 1957-1959
  - Leagues, 1954-1956
    - 1 of 2
    - 2 of 2
  - Legislation, 1953-1955
  - Lynching, Louisburg, N.C., 1935
  - Masons, Prince Hall Grand Lodge, Legal Research Fund
    - Annual reports, 1952-1962
    - Conference of Grand Masters, Newark, N.J., 1952
    - Correspondence (Box 112)
      - 1951
      - 1952
      - 1953
      - 1954
      - 1955
      - 1956
      - 1957 (Box 113)
      - 1958
      - 1959
    - Financial records
      - *Memoranda, 1951-1956
      - *Reports, 1951-1957
    - Memoranda, 1952-1960
    - Publications, 1951-1960
    - Reports, miscellaneous, 1949-1960
  - *Miller, Moses L., 1954
  - Miscegenation
    - Knight, Davis, 1948-1949
    - Miscellaneous cases, 1949-1955
  - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 114)
    - A
      - 1954
      - 1955-1957
      - 1958
      - 1959
      - 1960
      - 1961
    - B
      - * 1950-1952
      - 1954
      - 1955, 1957
      - 1958, Ba-Bl
      - 1958, Bo-Bu
      - 1959 (Box 115)
      - 1960
    - C
      - 1951-1953
      - 1954
      - * 1955-1961, (5 folders)
    - D (Box 116)
      - * 1951-1955
      - 1956
      - * 1958-1961, (2 folders)
    - *E, 1951-1960
    - *F, 1952-1960, (4 folders)
    - G (Box 117)
      - * 1951-1959, (2 folders)
      - 1960
      - * 1961, undated
    - H
      - * 1949-1959, (4 folders)
      - * 1960, undated (Box 118)
    - *I, 1954-1960
    - *J, 1950-1963, (4 folders)
    - *K, 1950-1960, (2 folders)
    - L
      - 1951-1955
      - * 1957-1960, (2 folders) (Box 119)
    - *M, 1951-1961, (5 folders)
    - *N, 1951-1960, undated
    - *O, 1951-1960 (Box 120)
    - *P, 1951-1961, (4 folders)
    - Q, 1953-1960
    - R
      - * 1951-1959, (3 folders)
      - * 1960-1961 (Box 121)
    - *S, 1949-1962, undated, (6 folders)
    - *T, 1952-1960, (2 folders) (Box 122)
    - *U, 1952-1960
    - *W, 1950-1960, (6 folders)
    - *Y-Z, 1958-1960, undated
  - Mississippi State Bar, 1964 (Box 123)
  - Moore, Harry T., 1951-1952 (bombing murder, Fla.) See also Container 52, Groveland, Fla.; and Container 127, Florida
    - Clippings, 1951-1952
    - Correspondence
      - General, 1951-1952
        - 1 of 2
        - 2 of 2
      - Meacham, Stewart and Charlotte, 1951-1952
      - Press, 1951-1952
    - Fund-raising
      - Contribution forms, 1952
      - Correspondence, 1951-1952
      - Miscellany, 1952
    - Hughes, Langston, "The Ballad of Harry Moore," 1952
    - Miscellany, 1952, undated
    - NAACP branches, 1951-1952 (Box 124)
    - Press releases, 1951-1952
    - Protest letters, 1951-1952
    - Protest meetings, 1952
      - 1 of 2
      - 2 of 2
    - Public relations
      - 1951, Dec.-1952, Jan.
      - 1952, Feb.-June
    - Publication drafts, 1952, undated
    - Statements, 1952, undated (Box 125)
    - Work stoppage, 1952
  - Moore, Ming & Leighton, Chicago, Ill., 1954
  - Murray, Philip, Memorial Foundation
    - Annual award, 1956-1959
    - Film project, 1954-1958
    - Funds, 1954-1955
  - National Community Relations Advisory Council, 1957-1958
  - National Civil Liberties Clearing House, 1955
  - National Funeral Directors Association, N.J., 1959
  - National Lawyers Guild, 1954-1956
  - National Medical Committee, 1953-1954
  - Navy See also Containers 40-44, Armed Forces
    - *Department, 1946-1956, (2 folders)
    - Seamen
      - *Braxton, John, 1955-1957
      - *Clark, Manuel, 1946-1954
      - Fuentes, Dilio, 1942-1945 (Box 126)
      - *Fullard, Jesse, 1954-1955
      - *Miscellaneous cases, 1952-1956, (3 folders)
      - Rollins, Walter, 1946-1953, undated
  - New York
    - Negro Ballet Co., undated
    - New York City Youth Board News, 1954-1955
    - Port of Embarkation, Army Transport Command, discharge cases, 1947-1950, undated
  - Pearson, C. O., 1952-1955
  - Property
    - *Coleman, Agnes, 1952-1953
    - *Knight, Amanda, 1950-1951
    - Miscellaneous cases
      - * 1950-1951
      - * 1952-1955, (4 folders) (Box 127)
    - *Sweett, Mattie, 1950-1951
    - *Turner, Samuel, 1954
    - *Turner v. Bragg (Mass.), 1950-1952
  - *Provost, Mary, 1951
  - *Psychiatric ward patients, 1957-1959
  - Racial tension
    - Florida, 1951-1953 See also Containers 52-54, Groveland, Fla.
    - Miscellaneous incidents, 1944-1953, undated
    - Mississippi
      - Correspondence, 1954-1955
      - Emmett Till case, 1955-1956 (Box 128)
      - Howard, T. R. M., 1955-1956
      - Lee, George W., 1955
    - Reports, miscellaneous, 1960-1961, undated
    - Riots See also Container 71, Detroit, Mich., Riot of 1943
      - Correspondence, 1944-1950
      - Publications and reports, 1944-1952
  - *Reubel, Eunice, 1955
  - Schools See also Containers 81-83, Education; and Containers 158-159, Teachers
    - General
      - Actions taken by states, 1951-1955, undated
      - Briefs, papers, and reports
        - 1952-1959
        - Undated
      - Correspondence
        - 1950-1953
        - 1954-1963
      - Desegregation, 1970-1972 (Box 129)
      - Memoranda, 1950-1959, undated
      - Miscellany, 1952-1958, undated
      - Newspaper clippings, 1948-1954, undated
      - President's Commission on Higher Education, undated
      - Printed material, 1950-1962, undated
      - Reargument of Supreme Court school desegregation cases, 1953-1954
      - Reports, 1955-1962, undated
      - Regional Action in Higher Education, 1951-1953
      - Secondary schools for Negroes, 1962
      - Southern Regional Council, "A Report on School Desegregation, 1960-1961," 1960
      - Teachers' rights, 1955-1956 (Box 130)
    - States
      - Alabama
        - Correspondence, 1950-1963
        - Davis v. Bd. of School Commissioners of Mobile Co., 1963
        - Henderson, Emmett L., 1945-1948
        - Hereford v. Huntsville Board of Education, 1962-1963
        - Koen v. Knight, 1962-1963
        - Lee v. Macon County Board of Education, 1955-1963
        - Miles College, Birmingham, 1962-1963
        - Miscellany, 1946-1955, undated
        - Mobile, 1955-1956
        - Nelson v. Grooms, 1962-1963
        - University of Alabama, Tuscaloosa, 1956, undated
      - Arizona, 1951-1954, undated
      - Arkansas
        - Correspondence
          - 1947-1958
          - 1959-1962, undated
        - Court filings, 1949 (Box 131)
        - Miscellany, 1948-1959, undated
      - California
        - Correspondence, 1951-1956
        - Miscellany, 1955, undated
        - Pasadena, 1951-1955
      - Colorado, 1956-1957, undated
      - Delaware
        - Belton v. Gebhart and Bulah v. Gebhart, 1951-1953
        - Correspondence, 1953-1961
        - Memoranda, 1953-1955
        - Miscellany, 1951-1955, undated
        - Redding, Louis, 1952-1955
        - School desegregation plans and reports, 1954-1959, undated
      - Florida
        - Correspondence, 1952-1961, undated
        - Gibson v. Dade County School Board of Education, 1956-1957 (Box 132)
        - Holmes County teacher dismissal, 1965
        - Miscellany, 1950-1956, undated
      - Georgia
        - Atlanta, 1950-1961
        - Calhoun v. Latimer, 1958-1959
        - Cheeseboro, Robert, 1953
        - Correspondence, 1950-1959
        - Georgia State College, Atlanta, 1956-1959 See also Container 220, Hunt v. Arnold
        - Memoranda, 1950-1959, undated
        - Miscellany, 1950-1959, undated
        - University of Georgia, Athens, 1959-1961
      - Illinois
        - Alton School, 1947-1953, undated
        - Cairo High School
          - Background material, 1952-1953, undated
          - Correspondence
            - Davis v. Schultz, 1952-1953 See also Container 197, same heading
            - General (Box 133)
              - 1951-1952
              - 1953-1954
            - Kendricks, Hattie B., reinstatement of, 1953-1954
          - Drafts and reports, undated
          - Memoranda, 1951-1954, undated
          - Miscellany, 1951-1953, undated
          - Press releases, 1952-1954
          - Printed material, 1950-1954, undated
        - Correspondence, 1951-1963
        - Memoranda, 1952-1957, undated
        - Miscellany, 1951-1957, undated
        - Pulaski County, 1952
        - Research material, undated
        - School desegregation reports, 1952-1956, undated
      - Indiana (Box 134)
        - Correspondence, 1952-1953
        - Miscellany, 1946-1953, undated
        - Reports, research drafts, and notes, 1946-1948, undated
      - Kansas
        - Brown v. Board of Education of Topeka
          - Background material, 1951-1954, undated
          - Correspondence
            - 1948, Sept.-1951, May
            - 1951, June
            - 1951, July-Dec.
            - 1952-1953
            - 1954-1955
          - Memoranda, 1948-1954
          - Miscellany, 1949-1951, undated
        - Correspondence, 1951-1954 (Box 135)
        - Miscellany, 1949-1953, undated
      - Kentucky
        - Correspondence, 1951-1957, undated
        - Louisville Municipal College
          - Correspondence, 1950-1951
          - Miscellany, 1935-1936, 1950-1951, undated
        - Miscellany, 1952-1956, undated
      - Louisiana
        - Correspondence
          - 1945-1952
          - 1953-1959
        - Louisiana Education Association, 1953-1954
        - Miscellany, 1945-1956, undated
      - Maryland
        - Correspondence, 1950-1960
        - Maryland State Teachers College, Towson, 1950-1951
        - Miscellany, 1950-1956, undated
        - Parker, Betty, 1950
        - St. Mary's County, 1955-1958
        - Testimony and opinion, 1950-1955, undated (Box 136)
        - University of Maryland, College Park, 1950-1951
      - Massachusetts
        - Miscellany, 1950-1954, undated
        - Springfield
          - Curricula outlines, 1943, undated
          - Printed material, 1940-1944, undated
      - Michigan, 1952-1960, undated
      - Miscellaneous, 1950-1959
      - Mississippi, 1950-1961, undated
      - Missouri
        - Brooks v. School District of the City of Moberly
          - Correspondence
            - 1955-1956
            - 1957-1959
          - Miscellany, 1955-1959, undated
        - Correspondence, 1948-1957
        - Miscellany, 1948-1956, undated (Box 137)
        - St. Louis
          - Correspondence, 1949-1950
          - Miscellany, 1947-1956
      - New Jersey
        - Correspondence, 1951-1957
        - Englewood
          - Correspondence, 1953-1955
          - Maps, 1953-1955 See Oversize
          - Miscellany, 1938, 1954-1955, undated
        - Miscellany, 1945-1953, 1961, undated
        - Printed material, 1952-1957
      - New Mexico, 1951-1955, undated
      - New York
        - Amityville, 1954-1957, undated
        - Brooklyn (Box 138)
          - Correspondence, 1955-1957
          - Information packet, 1956
          - Memoranda, 1955-1956
          - Miscellany, 1956-1957
        - Champlain College, Plattsburg, 1952-1953, undated
        - Corona, 1956, undated
        - Correspondence, 1949-1960
        - Department of Education, 1956-1960
        - Freeport School District No. 9, 1949-1951
        - Hempstead School District No. 1
          - Correspondence, 1948-1954
          - Letters to parents, undated
          - Memoranda, 1949-1951
          - Miscellany, 1948-1952
        - Intergroup Committee on New York's Public Schools
          - Agendas and minutes, 1955-1958
          - Conferences
            - "Children Apart," New York City, 1954
            - "For All Our Children," New York City, 1955
            - "Children Together," New York City, 1956
          - Correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 139)
          - Memoranda, 1954-1958
          - Miscellany, 1954-1956, undated
        - Jamaica School District, 1953-1954, undated
        - Memoranda
          - General, 1951-1959
          - Integration of New York City schools, 1956-1957
        - Miscellany, 1950-1957, undated See also Oversize
        - Public Education Association study, 1955
        - "Report of the Citizen's Committee on Racial Balance to the Mount Vernon Board of Education," 1963-1964
        - Traphagen School of Fashion, New York City, 1950
      - North Carolina (Box 140)
        - Caswell County, 1958-1959
        - Charlotte City School Board, 1948
        - Covington v. Edwards, 1958-1960 See also Container 193, same heading
        - Correspondence
          - 1950-1953
          - 1954-1956
          - 1957-1963, undated
        - Durham, 1958-1963
        - Holt v. Raleigh City Board of Education, 1958
        - Miscellany, 1950-1960, undated See also Oversize
        - Troy, 1954
      - Ohio, 1952-1956, undated
      - Oklahoma, 1952-1957
      - Pennsylvania (Box 141)
        - Chester
          - Correspondence, 1946, 1954-1955
          - Miscellany, 1914, 1946-1955, undated
          - *Retainer lists, 1954
        - Correspondence, 1952-1957
        - Girard College, Philadelphia
          - Correspondence, 1953-1959
          - Legal documents, 1957-1958
        - Miscellany, 1948-1956, undated
        - "Oxford Equality and Democracy," Lincoln University Student Chapter, NAACP, circa 1950
        - West Chester, 1939, 1954-1955, undated See also Oversize
        - Willow Grove, 1952-1955, undated See also Oversize
      - South Carolina
        - Clarendon County
          - Correspondence, 1951-1952
          - Miscellany, 1951-1952
        - Correspondence, 1947-1961 (Box 142)
        - Miscellany, 1947-1955, undated
      - Tennessee
        - Correspondence, 1950-1959
        - Goss v. Board of Education of Knoxville, 1959-1960 See also Container 201, same heading
        - University of Tennessee, Knoxville
          - Correspondence, 1950-1953
          - Miscellany, 1950-1960, undated
      - Texas
        - Correspondence
          - 1947-1952
          - 1953-1960
        - Dallas (Box 143)
          - 1956-1957
          - 1958-1959
          - 1960-1962
        - Euless, 1949-1951
        - Memoranda, 1949-1954
        - Miscellany, 1948-1955, undated
        - Newspaper clippings, 1949-1955, undated
        - San Antonio, 1952-1953
        - University of Texas, Austin, 1947-1953
      - United States military posts
        - Correspondence, 1953-1961
        - Memoranda, 1953-1954
        - Simmons v. Edwards, 1959-1961 See also Container 245, same heading
      - Virginia (Box 144)
        - Charlottesville
          - Adult Leadership Workshop on Desegregation, 1958
          - School case, 1958-1959
        - Correspondence
          - 1947-1950
          - 1951-1963
        - Court documents, 1946-1950, undated
        - Gray Commission, 1955-1956
        - King George County, 1946-1948
        - Memoranda, 1946-1959
        - Miscellany, 1947-1959, undated
        - Prince Edward County, Davis case
          - Correspondence
            - 1951-1952
            - 1953-1960
          - Trial transcript, 1952 (Box 145)
            - 1 of 2
            - 2 of 2
        - Reports, 1948-1959
      - West Virginia
        - Correspondence, 1950-1958
        - Miscellany, 1953-1956, undated
  - Sit-in demonstrations, 1960
  - Smith, A. Maceo, 1950-1954
  - Soldier troubles
    - Discharges
      - Dedmon, Jesse
        - *Cases, 1950-1954, (2 folders)
        - *Correspondence and reports, 1950-1954, (2 folders)
      - *Miscellaneous cases, 1950-1954, (4 folders) (Box 146)
      - Reeves, Frank See also Container 30, same heading
        - Discharge review cases
          - Air Force, 1954-1960
          - Army
            - * 1954
            - 1955-1960
          - Navy, 1954-1960
      - *Unfiled, 1956
    - Evans, James, 1955-1960
    - Individual cases (Box 147)
      - *Banks, James, 1950-1951
      - *Baynes, Claude, 1953
      - Bellot, Joseph
        - *Correspondence, 1944-1948
        - *Miscellany, 1944
      - *Bennett, John, 1955-1958
      - *Bostwick, Eugene, 1954
      - Boyce, Harold, 1951-1954
      - *Brewer, Fred, 1951-1953
      - *Brown, David, 1953
      - *Brown, Percy, 1949-1951
      - *Bullock, James, 1950-1952
      - Burns v. Wilson See also Container 188, same heading
        - *Cardiff, Ira, 1951-1955
        - Correspondence
          - 1949-1954
          - 1953-1954
        - *Dennis, Calvin, 1951-1954
        - Memoranda, 1950-1953, undated
        - Press releases and clippings, 1952-1955
      - Carter, Norman (Box 148)
        - *Correspondence, 1951-1953
        - Legal documents, 1949
      - *Cole, Frank, 1947-1953
      - Copeland, Raymond, 1955
      - Crosslin, Willis, 1951-1953
      - Crosslin, Paul, 1951-1953
      - Dandridge, Joseph, 1941-1952
      - Devone, James
        - *Correspondence, 1946-1947
        - Legal documents, 1946
      - *Dixione, Ario, 1954-1955
      - Fisher, Frank, and Edward Loury ("Army 'Scottsboro' case")
        - Correspondence, 1943-1945
        - Legal documents, 1944
        - Press releases and printed material, 1943-1944, undated
      - *Ford, Ruby, 1949-1951
      - Freeman, Edward, 1954 (Box 149)
      - *Gibson, Conner, 1956
      - *Gray, John, 1959-1960
      - *Green, Kenneth, 1953
      - *Grier, Ralph, 1946-1952
      - *Halsey, Everett, 1952-1954
      - *Harper, Marcellus, 1951-1953
      - *Harrell, Howard, 1954-1956
      - *Hart, James, 1957-1958
      - *Haste, Harry, 1952-1953
      - Hill, Charles, 1951, undated
      - Hill, Samuel, 1945-1949
      - *Holt, Milton, 1945-1950
      - *Johnson, Theodore, 1952-1956
      - *Jones, Willie, 1949-1954
      - *King, Nathaniel, 1950-1952
      - Landeros, Albert, 1955-1956
      - *Laster, Daniel, 1949-1952
      - *Lesesne, Sprunt, 1952-1953
      - *Mann, Joseph, and Albert Myers, 1953-1955
      - *Marcial, Joseph, 1951-1952
      - *McGary, Leroy, 1944-1955 (Box 150)
      - *Nelson, W. H., 1955
      - *Nichols, Russell, 1956
      - *Norris, Willie, 1951-1952
      - *Osborn, Floyd, 1951-1952
      - *Ramsey, Dallas, 1944-1951
      - *Reese, Charles, 1957-1958
      - *Riggins, James Lee, and Chastine Beverly, 1951-1953
      - *Ruffin, William, 1951
      - *Sanders, Edna, 1954
      - *Shanklin, Norman, 1952
      - *Smithey, Robert, 1956-1958
      - *Spear, Ben, 1943-1951
      - Spurling, Roy
        - *Correspondence, 1953
        - *Legal documents, 1952
      - *Steen, Leroy, 1949-1951
      - *Tapp, James, 1945-1953
      - *Thompson, Clifford, 1953-1954
      - *Todd, James, 1945
      - *Towns, Donald, 1951-1954
      - Turner, James (Box 151)
        - *Correspondence, 1947-1951
        - Legal documents, 1948-1951, undated
      - *Walker, Herbert, 1953
      - Walker, Lawrence, 1951
      - Washington, George
        - *Correspondence, 1953
        - *Legal documents, 1952
      - Watson, Jackie
        - *Correspondence, 1954
        - *Legal documents, 1953
      - Whiteside, Henry
        - *Correspondence, 1947
        - *Legal documents, 1946
      - *Whyte, Joe, 1951
      - *Williams, Elias, 1948
      - *Willis, Lawrence, 1953-1956 (Box 152)
      - *Wilson, Joseph, 1953
      - *Wise, Frederick, 1945, 1952
    - Korea See also Container 18, Korean trip; Container 43, Korean War; Container 99, Korea, defense fund; and Container 225, Korean War and World War II Court Martial Records
      - Greenberg, Jack, 1950-1952
      - Individual cases
        - *Baber, William H., 1951-1952
        - *Bryant, Carsin, 1951-1953
        - *Butler, Thomas, 1951-1952
        - *Drummond, Harry B., 1950-1953
        - Gilbert, Leon
          - *Correspondence, 1950-1953, (2 folders)
          - Legal documents, 1950, undated
          - Press clippings and releases, 1950-1951
        - *Harris, Harold, 1951-1953
        - *Harvey, Bennie, and Austin Wilson, 1951-1953
        - *Hubbard, James, 1951-1954
        - *Paulfrey, Peter, 1950-1951
        - *Reed, Nathaniel, 1950-1954
        - Riddick, John (Box 153)
          - *Correspondence, 1951-1954, (2 folders)
          - Legal documents, undated
        - *Rowland, James, 1952-1953
        - *Simmons, Willie, 1950-1952
        - *Williams, Luther, 1950-1953
      - Judge Advocate General, 1950-1953
      - List of court martial cases, undated
      - Marshall, Thurgood
        - Press releases, 1950-1951
        - "Report on Korea," 1951
        - Speaking tour
          - Correspondence
            - 1950-1951
            - 1951
          - Memoranda and printed material, 1950-1951
        - Trip to Korea (Box 154)
          - Correspondence, 1950-1951
          - Memoranda, 1950-1951
      - *Miscellaneous court martial cases, "A-W," 1950-1954, (3 folders)
    - Miscellaneous cases
      - *A-B, 1951-1963, (5 folders)
      - *C-H, 1946, 1951-1963, (11 folders) (Box 155)
      - *I-P, 1950-1963, (13 folders) (Box 156)
      - *R-Y, 1950-1963, (12 folders) (Box 157)
    - Police brutality, 1951-1955 (Box 158)
  - South Africa, railway case, 1953
  - Southern Conference Educational Fund
    - Publications, 1952-1956
    - "Southwide Conference on Compliance with the Supreme Court Decision on Segregation in Public Schools," 1955
  - Southern Education Reporting Service, 1955
  - Southern Regional Council, 1959-1963
  - Southern Regional Educational Board publications, 1955-1956
  - Taft-Hartley Act, 1947-1953
  - Teachers See also Containers 81-83, Education; and Containers 128-145, Schools
    - Michigan, 1955
    - Salary cases
      - Georgia
        - Davis v. Cook See also Containers 195-196, same heading
          - Bulletins and clippings, 1941-1950, undated
          - Correspondence
            - 1940-1946
            - 1947-1951, undated
      - Miscellany, 1941-1954, undated
      - Mississippi (Box 159)
        - Bates v. Batte See also Container 183, same heading
          - Correspondence
            - 1945-1948
            - 1949
            - 1950
            - 1951-1952
          - Memoranda, 1947-1952
          - Miscellany, 1950-1952, undated
          - Press releases and clippings, 1946-1951, undated
        - Review of teacher salary cases, 1945-1949
      - West Virginia, 1947-1951, undated
    - Tennessee, 1955-1956
    - Tenure laws, historical review
      - Alabama, 1955
      - Arkansas, 1953-1954, undated
      - Delaware, 1955
      - Virginia, 1955-1959
    - Union, New York, N.Y., 1955
  - Tobias, Channing, 1954 (Box 160)
  - Transportation
    - Airports
      - Brisbane v. High Point Airport Authority, 1957-1959
      - Civil Aeronautics Administration, 1955-1957, undated
      - Miscellaneous cases, 1949-1957, undated
    - Bus companies
      - Boycotts
        - Montgomery, Ala., Browder v. Gayle, 1956-1957
        - Tallahassee, Fla., 1956, undated
      - Flemming v. South Carolina Electric Co., 1955-1957 See also Container 200, same heading
        - Correspondence, 1955-1957
        - Press releases and clippings, 1955-1956
      - Greyhound, 1950-1957
      - McGlockton, Edward, 1951-1954
      - Miscellaneous cases
        - 1951-1956
        - 1957-1958
      - North Carolina v. Jackson, 1954-1955 See also Container 241, same heading (Box 161)
      - Payne, Fred, 1951-1955
      - Saxon v. Smokey Mountain Stages, Inc., 1949-1953
      - Speed v. City of Tallahassee, Fla., 1957-1958
      - Williams v. Georgia Public Service Comm'n, 1957-1958
    - Correspondence
      - 1951, Jan.-June
      - 1951, July-Dec.
      - 1953-1955
      - 1956-1957
    - Hurley, Ruby, 1955
    - Interstate Commerce Commission See also Containers 96-97, same heading
      - General, 1950-1957
      - LeFlore, John L., railway case, 1952-1954